<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>thatsn0tmysite</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on thatsn0tmysite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 21:35:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Go(ogle) Play Books</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/04/google-play-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 21:35:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/04/google-play-books/</guid>
      <description>The title is kind of a very bad pun, one of the &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s not even funny&amp;rdquo; ones. So, what is today&amp;rsquo;s post about? Google.
No, not the privacy concerns or the data usage policies, nor their silly Google Play Store rules. Not the tracking, not the fact that their products seem to be walking dead bodies before they reach their prime time (looking at you Stadia)&amp;hellip; but books.
I recently decided to download back all the e-books which I so carefully uploaded over the year to their Books service back&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public disclosures</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/03/public-disclosures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 22:37:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/03/public-disclosures/</guid>
      <description>Well, as mentioned in the last post, some lame XSS I found just went public.
For those wanting to jump straight to the point:
 muoversiaroma.it romamobile.it travel.mob.cotralspa.it servizi.cotralspa.it  I am a firm believer in the philosophy of &amp;ldquo;disclose as you please&amp;rdquo;, for the vulnerabilities above, I decided to attempt and be as ethical as possible and tried to disclose them responsibly.
That attempt failed.
Apparently what a researcher thinks is going to happen and what actually happens not always matches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First commit</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/03/first-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 02:18:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/03/first-commit/</guid>
      <description>For the few souls that ever followed my blog: I finally migrated. There was no real reason to keep a wordpress blog, as I really never used any features from Wordpress.
I migrated to Github pages, because&amp;hellip; free hosting, and custom domains. Seemed nice enough to me, also for some reason I ended up using Hugo, over Jekyll. I could never get Jekyll to run even thought the setup is actually almsot the same as Hugo&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I will eventually write something about me here&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
